#### Contact

udcarkangel@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ maurosaldagarcia (LinkedIn)

#### Skills

Front-End Developer VueJs ReactJs Tailwind CSS

## Languages

Inglés (Professional Working) Spanish (Native or Bilingual) EF-SET in LinkedIn

Phone and WhatsApp (+57) 322 412 4297

# Mauricio Saldarriaga Garcia

Front-End Developer | VueJs | ReactJs | Tailwind CSS | Crypto Enthusiast

Bogotá, Distrito Capital, Colombia

# Front-End Developer Jr.

I am interested in working as a developer or Front-End Developer, remotely from anywhere in the world (relocation available), I have a high level of English language, listening and writing, medium level of conversation, development of web projects, using VueJs, ReactJs, Tailwind, MySQL, Mongo DB, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, postman, Git.

At this moment I have an internship contract with GoldenSec Colombia, working as Front-End Developer Jr., VueJs and Tailwind are the technologies used by the company also work with Machile learning Algorithms in python.

I have 1 year of experience as a Web designer in WordPress and Joomla systems, MySQL databases and positioning (SEO).

15 years of experience in hardware, networks, VPN and maintenance, 8 years as a volunteer Cultural Manager in the city of Medellín in Comunidad Underground and Fiesta Friki (volunteering), currently studying Analysis and Development of Information Systems at SENA.(Waiting for degree)

GitHub repository with current projects. https://github.com/RedStabros

# Experience

Goldensec Colombia SAS - A GSS Company Front-End Developer Jr. september 2022 - Present (6 months) - Remote

Red Cultural Juvenil
Coordinator of Digital Media and IT
Include 1 year of web Developer
march of 2013 - Present (10 years)

#### Autonomous

Microcomputer Systems Technician junio de 2008 - septiembre de 2022 (14 years 4 months) Bogotá, Distrito Capital, Colombia

#### **ODONTOSS**

Systems Manager july of 2012 - june of 2018 (6 years) Medellín, Antioquia, Colombia

Purchase, maintenance and repair of computer equipment, installation and maintenance of networks and systems, creation and maintenance of the company's internal VPN, camera systems and remote access.

# Education

Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje (SENA)

Analysis and Development of Information Systems, Information

Technology · (may of 2020 - december of 2022)

### Universidad El Bosque

Developer Mintic 2022, Computer software and multimedia applications · (may of 2021 - december of 2021)

#### Platzi

Basic programming course, Software Engineering · (2018 - 2018)

## Universidad de Antioquía

Audiovisual and Multimedia Communication · (2012 - 2017)